[opening theme music playing]
BLOOD IN THE DISCO BALL
[news anchor] It's been nearly two weeks
since the gray wolf Legoshi,
has been on the run.
First question on my mind is.
what are the police doing?
Well, clearly they're slacking.
I mean, come on, if they still
can't find him, that tells me
he's gotta be hiding somewhere
in the black market. Right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. That does makes sense.
If I were a criminal, I'd hide myself
in a place that police
wouldn't be able to search.
That might be one of the reasons
the police announced they'll pay
ten million Yen
to anyone who can provide information
leading to his arrest.
That's the highest reward
in our history, isn't it?
Absolutely. But if he did commit more
than 20 violent crimes...
He was at the restaurant six days a week.
Twenty crimes seems impossible.
Forget about the Zoolympics,
isn't more important to make sure
our citizens are safe first and foremost?
- [anchors continues]
- [phone line ringing]
Yeah, it's the Mayor.
Turns out that gray wolf is going to
show up tomorrow
at the Black Market turf war.
Capture him, no matter what.
Right.
Up to you, dead or alive.
How could he?! [groans]
[whimpers]
It was obvious he only ever cared about
power and profit...
but I never expected my father
to try and get there through bribery.
He's as twisted as the horns on his head!
I can't stand it!
- [breathing heavily]
- Louis, sir...
You gonna tell me to stay quiet too?
[groans] Not at all...
[cellphone vibrating]
[sighs]
Hey, Chloe.
[Chlo] I found it.
Exactly what you wanted.
-It's here, but...
- Fantastic. That's great to hear.
How about I stop by and see you tomorrow?
We'll chat about this then.
[Chloe sighs] Unbelievable!
-Just like your father...
- What?
- Did my father do something?
- Tomorrow, then!
[line disconnects]
[sighs in exasperation]
I'm sorry. That was uncalled for.
Forgive me, sir.
You should know
this isn't what your father really wants.
Unfortunately, he's being threatened.
Wait, what are you saying?
Apparently, the mayor did some digging
through your past with your father.
I hear he found something
rather troubling.
[sighs in surprise]
The Black Market catalogue?
He swore to me he'd throw that away.
It's important you understand
your father's actions.
I assure you, he wanted no part of this.
Well, thank you for that.
If this part of my past got out,
it'd stain the foundation.
You're not understanding.
It's about you.
Your father is worried about you, Louis.
About me?
Yes.
He won't stand by
and allow your future to be destroyed.
He actually cares?
[Jimma breathing heavily]
Look at all that meat!
I know, dammit!
[groans] I can't take it anymore!
Calm down!
Here, why dontcha chew on Louis' antler?
It's on me.
Didn't mean to keep you waiting.
I'm surprised you're able to show up
on time
for anything riding that junk heap.
She's still got plenty of miles in her.
Tell me what it is we're doing here.
I can only assume
since you went out of your way...
I take it it's about your grandson.
[grunts softly] Well, you've still got it.
[paper rustling]
This letter right here is from Legoshi.
So uh...
"I hope things are going well.
I wanted to talk to you in person,
but that's not possible at the moment.
I appreciate you
continuing to take care of Haru.
But remember to take care of yourself,
while you're at it.
Legoshi."
It was The Five Hundred Cornered Rats
who delivered it.
Aren't those little critters your friends?
Maybe those rodents know something?
What do you think's behind this letter?
Suicide note?
[grunts softly]
I'm definitely worried about him.
I hope he's not planning anything crazy.
If Legoshi makes a move
he'll fall right into our net.
Huh? Ya wanna let me in on the plan here?
Well, he's a wanted criminal.
We'll arrest him.
- I appreciate you providing information.
- Hang on!
You know he didn't do a damn thing!
- Alright, Corne, its time.
- Hey, what are you doin', Yahya?!
Looks like he's making a move.
He's aiming for the Black Market.
- Issue the orders.
- You dirty slime bag!
I was an idiot thinking I could trust you!
You never change, do you, old friend?
What a shame.
[Melon laughing]
[Giant legoshi growling]
[both growling]
[gasps]
- [sighs]
- [heavy breathing]
[sighs]
- [metal clinging]
- [groans]
The leopard in me
grows and the gazelle retreats...
Oh Melon, you seem lost in thought.
[Melon] Just the two of us,
in the strange fairy-tale world
mother made for us
to escape from real life...
Living in make believe.
Melon, my darling...
[Melon] I loved just hearing mom
say my name.
In those moments
I wasn't a carnivore or an herbivore...
I was just myself... just Melon.
[mother] Your timid little face...
and that frail body of yours.
You remind me so much of your daddy.
I just adored
everything about that gazelle.
[licks lips]
[sighs]
She was my everything...
her terrifying beauty...
The gazelle inside of me is disappearing.
[strains]
[Louis] Very impressive facilities.
Even a smoking room.
I suppose.
What happened between you and my father?
[Chloe sighs]
Let me guess.
Something about the artificial meat?
Oh, so you know about that?
There was some drama.
When I gave him the lab results, he said:
"This cannot be allowed to stand,
I'll leak it to the media!"
He was really worked up about it.
[scoffs]
What is she talking about?
- So, what exactly did you tell him?
- Only the truth.
The lab results confirmed
the artificial meat wasn't
fully lab-grown,
turns out some of it
is from early stage embryos.
[Louis] That's insane...
But the very next day,
he gave me strict orders
to never speak of it again.
- Well that's suspicious.
- Yeah.
Like someone threatened him into silence.
From what I could tell,
he seemed to be suffering.
[Yuta] You should know
this isn't what your father really wants.
Unfortunately, he's being threatened.
Anyway, regarding
the blood coagulation inhibitor drug,
I've got a delivery update for you.
Yes?
Earliest I can get it in your hands
would be two days.
[stutters] Why the delay?
[Chloe] We can't just take anything
we want.
There's an application process.
Two days isn't going to work.
I need it tonight.
- Tonight?
- My friend, uh...
he's fighting a duel.
And what does your friend fighting a duel
have to do with blood clotting?
It has to do with his opponent.
He's the one behind all these
serial devourings.
- What?
- He's a very powerful hybrid.
By mixing herbivore and carnivore blood,
we discovered his weakness.
And we need this edge.
When you mix the blood
of different species,
it clots instantly, right?
I get it now. And I really would
love to be able to help you--
[Louis] I made a promise...
that I would fight too.
Why would you fight?
Because his pain is also my pain.
Every time he has to fight,
he does it alone.
He never hesitates
to put himself in danger.
Especially to protect someone
he cares for.
No matter how lost he gets,
in the end he always faces things head-on.
At the same time, I do the opposite.
I stand there doing nothing
while those I care about get hurt.
You really want to help the guy,
don't you?
It's the right thing to do.
Maybe we're cowards for trying to use
this "blood trick".
Still, sometimes you can't win
by fighting fair.
I think you're in the right.
"In the right..."
[sighs]
But am I though?
[scoffs] No.
Legoshi would never do things this way.
There's no way I can go through with this.
Hold on.
I can't be a coward.
I've got to do this with honor.
[gasps]
That's final.
That's who I am.
It's so clear to me.
I have to fight my own enemy.
Isn't that right, Legoshi?
I appreciate you.
Excuse me.
I know what I have to do. We'll talk soon.
Hey, wait, uh...
Hang on!
[sighs]
Are you sure you're an herbivore?
Your blood's way too hot.
GIANT PANDA
[Legoshi] You're a life saver.
You're the only one I could trust.
So thank you for doing this, Mr. Gohin.
Oh, come on.
Didn't you almost get killed twice?
I wonder if you'll ever learn...
Yeah, but, I came back to life both times.
Can't say I get it.
When people fight they normally reach
for weapons and armor.
But you drain your own blood,
and pull out your own fangs.
You'd think you'd wanna be
in your best shape.
Crazy.
In my experience,
I found my best weapons
haven't necessarily been the gifts
I was born with as a carnivore.
It's not my traits as a wolf,
these claws and fangs.
It's everything I've experienced and felt.
That's what I lean on.
[sighs]
That enough to protect
what you want to protect?
I'll prove it is.
The next time I see my reflection
in Haru's eyes,
I wanna see a wolf I respect.
If it's for that,
then I can fight.
Come on.
You never change, do you?
Thank you for your help.
[grunts] Try not to die.
You owe me money for the dental work.
[chuckles]
[announcer] It's now time
to introduce each of the gangs!
With pride as high as their heels!
The big sisters of the Black Market,
the Inari-Gumi!
[man] Ten!
Now the flashy and extravagant samurai!
Loyalty and brotherhood... The Madara-Gumi!
Covered in scales
as strong as their bonds!
Rugged and independent... the Doku-Gumi!
Next! Will these champions from last year
be able to defend their throne?
The kings of the beasts... Shishi-Gumi!
And for the first time in 30 years,
we have a newcomer!
The gray wolf, Legoshi!
Hey, isn't that wolf wanted for devouring?
With a ten-million bounty.
Let's grab him then!
[announcer] The rules are simple!
We ignite each contestant's blood.
The brightness and shape of the flame,
as well as the strength of the scent,
will decide the winner!
The winner earns the seat of
Black Market leader for one full year.
On top of that,
they will receive this special prize
of meat!
[gasping]
Wow...talk about delicious!
[smirks]
Is everything ready?
Alright then... Ignite!
[crowd cheering]
Gotta be Inari-Gumi.
No, Madara-Gumi for sure.
It's Doku-Gumi!
Shishi-Gumi's scent
is kind of weak this year.
[Ten chuckles]
Look at you lions
breaking new ground by putting
an herbivore of all things on the throne,
but it seems
you've gotten a little soft this year.
Ahh!
I don't believe I've introduced myself.
[hissing] How rude of me.
My name is Melon
and I'm the new boss of the Shishi-Gumi.
Pleased to make your acquaintance.
So I guess you ended up
with the short straw, huh?
Shishi-Gumi's time is over.
Really?
Watch yourself.
Underestimating us
isn't the smartest move.
That would be a fatal mistake.
[laughing]
Consider yourself warned!
[sniff] Ahh...
the truth is, Shishi-Gumi's scent
is pathetically weak.
I must admit.
Guess I'll add to it.
- [grunts]
- [groans]
Agata, no!
Agata!
You crazy bastard!
How could you?
[Jimma gasps]
Boss...
This will give us
the strongest scent, right?
- [male] Shishi-Gumi!
- Yeah.
What do you think you're doing?
That's against the rules!
[grunts]
The nonsense of these silly turf wars
should be against the rules!
We love blood, and meat,
let's celebrate it!
You all want meat, right?
You want to eat the meat, sure!
So then why would you settle
for just the smell!?
Come on, wake up already!
- That's right!
- Today is Meat Appreciation Day!
[groans]
You all love meat, don't you?
That's why you're here
in the Black Market!
Damn straight! Yeah!
[Melon laughing maniacally]
What kind of beast are you
if you don't embrace your instincts?
Accept the thing you love,
Black Market!
Rule violation! Restrain him!
[commotion]
I think I get it...
Anything goes tonight.
I'll let loose a little bit.
What do ya say?
This gets my blood pumping!
Legoshi,
this will be your final night.
Why not make it spectacular?
[laughing maniacally]
It's nice, but weren't there more
dinosaurs last year?
The ones Cherryton School makes.
[female] I heard that school's
had a lot of trouble lately.
- Huh, like what?
- I don't really know the details...
This is my first time at a land festival.
[Seven] Surely Legoshi wouldn't show up
at a place this crowded, right?
Maybe, but we made a promise,
that he and I
would light a candle here together.
Well, he strikes me as a kid
that keeps promises.
Hey, which direction is the wind blowing?
[licks]
[sniffs]
Hmm, it's blowing in from the ocean.
[groans] Mind if we move upwind?
So Legoshi can find me by my scent.
She can be pretty assertive, huh?
Land creatures have legs
that they use to walk on the ground.
The way someone walks reveals their heart.
And I definitely know how she feels...
She's in love.
[Mayor] And also, switch these two.
I'll get right on it, sir.
[announcer] Everyone!
This year's Festival of the Meteor
is finally here!
[announcement continues]
FESTIVAL OF THE METEOR TIME SCHEDULE
3. SURPRISE ANNOUNCEMENT (FOOD)
I guess they're about to announce
the news about lab-grown meat.
[sighs]
Louis, it's up to you, buddy.
We're counting on you.
Just leave it to me.
Oh no, I think it's starting!
Hurry, aren't you done?
[grunts] Lift it up a little higher.
[straining]
[Fudge] A little higher!
[gasps]
Okay! We're good!
Put it down.
Huh?
[Sanu] Good work everybody.
[all] Sanu!
[Sanu] Anything else we need to do?
- Has the tech crew checked lighting?
- I'll flip the breaker!
- Makeup?
- We're about to start.
[Sheila] Leave it to me.
Are the tools over there?
Yes, over there!
[panting]
Has anyone seen where Pina's at?
Isn't he hanging out with girls
from the other schools?
[Miguno] Jeez!
You took forever to fix your ear fur.
That's why we're late.
Of course I did!
Gotta look good for the ladies!
Y'all hungry? I already made a menu!
How much are you gonna eat, bro?
[Miguno] I can't wait! I covered a band
at last year's school festival
that's playing tonight!
[Kolo] Heck yeah! Jack are you ready to--
WANTED: - CHARGE: MURDER
[sighs softly]
[all gasp]
[panting]
[Legoshi] This is crazy!
[screams]
You're not getting away!
[groans]
Oh, Grandpa...
Who do you think you're calling "Grandpa"?
[both grunting]
[Savon] Komodo dragon venom
doesn't do it for ya, huh?
Fists and tail it is, then.
Little boy.
[gasps] Beautiful...
I feel so safe...
like being hugged by Grandpa.
[thud, groans]
[Savon chuckles]
Come on, kid,
I hope this isn't you putting up a fight.
[spits]
[whimpering]
[commotion]
I'm outta here!
[thud, groans]
- [grunts]
- [screams]
We can't fight in here!
We'll both be crushed!
[Savon chuckles] Worry about yourself!
- [grunts]
- [groans]
What's a fight without a little danger?
If you fight, expect to get hurt,
expect pain and-- [gasps]
[groaning]
The more wounded a creature gets,
the more beautiful that creature becomes!
[both grunt softly]
[sighs] Maybe our values are kind of...
- kind of similar in a way?
- [Savon grunts]
You and me ain't done.
Our spirits are a lot stronger
than this crumbling rock.
Take this.
Whoa.
Woah, it's wiggling around!
It's freshly severed,
so it's still got some life.
This is a message from the Doku-Gumi.
- You're welcome, kid.
- Huh?
This is a message?
"The beasts of the Black Market...
don't deserve such an easy heart."
Huh?
- [beeping]
- [gasps]
[groans]
[closing tune playing]